Now let's discuss how discuss how Audacity could apply these other
现在 我们来讨论下 Audacity 如何使用
techniques, to either validate metrics from the customer funnel we talked about
这些技巧用于验证我们之前谈到的客户漏斗中的指标
previously, or brain storm new metrics that are not covered by the funnel.
或漏斗中未涵盖的头脑风暴中产生的新指标
At the top of the funnel, audacity could compare the count
在漏斗顶部 audacity 可以比较
of how many users visit their website to externally available metrics,
网站的用户访问量与
from companies like comScore or Hit Wise.
来自 comScore 或 Hit Wise 等公司的外部可用指标
Audacity could also look at the completion rate of classes and
Audacity 可以查看每门课程的完成率
compare that to externally available data.
并将它和外部可用数据进行比较
If Audacity sees that a particular lesson is getting a very low completion
如果 Audacity 发现某一门课程的完成率非常低
rate, they might do a UER study to investigate that.
他们可能会进行用户体验研究来调查原因
Watching the students try to complete the lesson can help you figure out, do
看着学员试着完成一门课程能够帮助你判断
the students understand where to click, can they find everything on the screen,
学员是否知道点击哪里 能否在屏幕上找到所有信息
are they progressing in order, how do they interact with the coach?
他们是否在有序地学习课程 如何与辅导员进行互动
You might see users twiddling their thumbs, waiting for a video to load and
你可能会看到用户转动拇指 等待视频下载
that might give you an idea that you should be tracking the latency.
这些可能是向你暗示 你应该跟踪延迟时间了
If you observe that people aren't seeing the instructors notes below the video,
如果你观察到人们没有看视频下方的讲师注释
then you might want to use percentage of people who click on the link
你可以使用点击链接的百分比
as the metric, or
作为一个指标
if latency looks like an issue then that's a metric you could track.
或如果延迟时间看起来是个问题 那么这就是你可以跟踪的一个指标
For any metric that you come up with during a UER session,
对于在用户体验研究会话期间你想到的指标
you might want to validate that metric with a retrospective analysis
你可能想通过回顾性分析方法验证
to see how that metric has varied over time.
看看这个指标如何随着时间变化
Or you might want to run some new experiments and
或者你可能想要实施一些新的实验
see how that metric varies as you make changes.
看看这个指标是如何随着你做出的变更发生变化的
And finally, the bottom level of the funnel, whether students get jobs and,
最后 在漏斗底层 学员是否找到了工作
if they do, do the audacity classes help is an example of an unmeasurable metric.
如果找到了 Audacity 的课程是否有帮助 这是无法测量的一个指标
In this case surveys might help, maybe via email or on repeat students.
在这里 通过邮件或对再次学习课程的学生进行调查可能有所帮助
For example, you could ask students if the material covered in class was
例如 你可能会问学员 在被问及的面试问题中
touched on in any interview questions there were asked.
是否涉及课堂中涵盖的材料
Like I mentioned before, surveys are often useful for
就像我之前提到的 调查对于捕捉这种不能直接测量的指标
capturing metrics like these, that it's not possible to measure directly.
通常非常有用
The main issue, though, is that you can't directly compare the numbers from
但 主要问题是你不能将调查中的数字
a survey to what you get from any other measurements.
和其他测量中得到的数字直接进行比较
The biggest issue here is that the populations for
这里最大的问题是
your internal metrics and your surveys might not be comparable.
内部指标和调查的人数不匹配
You might be reaching a biased population with your survey
相对于参加课程的群体而言 你调查涉及的群体
relative to the population taking the class.
可能有失偏颇
Let's also go over the cases you saw before of metrics that were tricky to
我们回顾一下你之前看到的 指标难以测量的几种情况
measure, and go over some other techniques you could use.
然后回顾一下你能够使用的一些技巧
I had mentioned before that if Audacity wants to measure the rate of students
我之前曾提到过 如果 Audacity 想测量
returning to take a second course, they could definitely track this metric long
学员返回来学习第二门课程的比率 他们肯定会长期跟踪这个指标
term, but they might not be able to use it for individual experiments.
但他们可能不会将其用于单个实验
So, Audacity might follow up with a survey,
因此 Audacity 可能会再进行一次调查
to see what causes users to return.
看看什么原因造成用户返回来学习另一门课程
Then, if they can find something measurable that predicts returning well
然后 如果他们能够找到可测量指标 认为学生是由于正面原因而返回学习的
they could use that as a proxy in their experiments.
他们就能够在实验中将它当作代替指标
For the shopping site trying to measure the average happiness of shoppers,
对于尝试测量购物者平均幸福指数的购物网站
this is the metric that they probably can't track even long term, but again,
这是一个他们可能不会长期跟踪的指标
they can try to find signals that correlate with what they really want.
但他们可以尝试寻找与他们真正想要什么产品相关的信号
They could instrument their website to pop us a survey at
他们可以在用户每次购买行为结束后弹出一个调查
the end of every purchase, or they could run a small UER and
或实施小型的用户体验研究
use this data to brainstorm some metrics they could use.
用这个数据共同讨论他们可以使用的一些指标
For the search engine that wants to measure whether users are finding
对于想要测量用户是否找到所需信息的搜索引擎
the information they're looking for, there are a lot of possible proxies.
有很多可用的代替指标
They might be able to use, for example,
他们可以使用 例如
the length of time spent on the search page.
在搜索页面花费的时间长度
Whether the user clicked on any results that were shown or
用户是否点击显示的任何结果或
whether there were any follow-up queries trying to get at the right information
是否有试着用不同的方式获取正确信息的
in a different way.
后续询问
You might be able to identify which of these proxies are more promising by
你都能够通过
looking at external data about Information finding research or
查看关于信息发现研究或
by running a UER study.
实施用户体验研究的外部数据 确定哪些代替指标更好
Now we didn't discuss this but another very common technique in this situation,
现在 我们没有讨论这个 讨论的是在这种情况下另一个非常常用的指标
probably the most common,
可能是最常用的
is human evaluation where you pay human raters to evaluate your site.
也就是人工评估 你需要向人工评估员付费评估你的网站
This technique is covered in more detail in the PDF linked
在讲师注释链接的 PDF 中对这个技巧
in the instructor's notes.
有更详细的介绍
Next, for each of the following scenarios,
接下来 为以下每个情景
choose which techniques you would use to generate metrics.
选择你会使用哪些技巧生成指标
First, suppose Audacity wants one or
首先 假设 Audacity 想要用一个或
more metrics to measure user engagement in their classes.
多个指标测量其课程中的用户参与度
They could look at course completion.
他们能够查看课程完成情况
But that's a long term metric.
但那是个长期指标
So it would be nice to come up with more detailed metrics.
因此 最好想出一些更详细的指标
What techniques would you use to either brainstorm or
你会使用什么指标集体讨论或
evaluate potential metrics?
评估潜在指标？
Second, suppose a shopping site sells local food products and
其次 假设一个购物网站出售当地食品
they want to decide whether to extend their inventory.
他们想决定是否扩大库存
Maybe they should add new flavors of coffee?
或许他们应该增加新口味的咖啡
Or maybe they should start a whole new line, such as cookbooks
或者 他们应该开启一条全新的产品线 如食谱
How could the site measure interest and potential new problems?
网站如何测量有趣的潜在的新问题？
Finally, suppose you wanted to test the placement of an advertisement on your
最后 假设你想测试一个广告在你网站上的位置
site, and so you wanted to know which ads are getting the most views.
你想知道哪些广告的浏览人数最多
It's hard to tell what users are looking at, so
很难判断用户在寻找什么
what techniques could you use to come up with a proxy?
那么 你能使用什么技巧想出一个代替指标？
Choose from these techniques, which we just discussed.
从我们刚刚讨论的这些技巧中选择
External data, a user experience research study, a focus group,
外部数据、用户体验研究、焦点小组
a survey, retrospective analysis, or running a new experiment.
调查、回顾性分析或运行一个新实验
It's probably possible to use all of these techniques in some way or another.
你也可以以不同方式使用所有的这些技巧
But for each scenario, pick the two techniques you think are the most
为每个情景选择两个你认为最有用的技巧
promising and write the corresponding number in these boxes.
并在这些方框中写下对应的编号